GRAPHIC DESIGNER / <WEBDESIGNER>

castano.cindy1@gmail.com 104 avenue de clichy +33(0)6 34 55 45 08 75017 Paris



Print & web designer for more than 5 years, I like to bring meaning to the design. Storytelling is the basis of a relevant visual that will meet the communication objectives. I like working on issues related to interface design and global design. UX & UI, site design & artistic direction. I am meticulous, organized, and I know how to be a source of proposals.

EDUCATION

> 2015 - 2016

Webdesign's education (graduate)

Itecom 75002, Fr

> 2013 - 2015

BTS Graphic Design (graduate)

ES2A 75015, Fr

Art school

ES2A 75015, Fr

> 2009 - 2011

Photography's Education

Lignes & formation

Baccalaureate in Literature (graduate)

High school, Valence, Fr

COMPÉTENCES























WORK EXPERIENCE

> Jan 2019 - Today

Freelance for C2 Atelier Design

Paris 09

- Webdesign
- UX / UI
- Web development HTML / CSS / JQuery / JS
- Responsive Design

Clients: PremierAppart / Vaslin / Quitoque

> Apr 2018 - Sept 2018

Freelance for La petite Com

Pontoise

- Webdesign
- UX / UI software
- Logo
- Responsive Design

Clients: Afhymage / Aéroclub de Nangis / Valony / Takiti / Backup rent / Unexpected Consilium

> Nov 2016 - Apr 2018

Freelance

Paris

- Edition
- Webdesign
- Web development HTML / CSS / JQuery / JS

Clients: Collectif 9901 / MathsMelisso / Isi Vertie / DC11331

> Sept 2013 - Oct 2016

Artistic Director for MathsMelisso

Paris 75015

- Book layout
- Graphic conception
- Visual identity
- Flvers
- Brochure